字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
最快首发美剧日剧下载请登录
字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：王大可 晨星晓Reginamoon Charl 小暴徒 木浅 想名字好难 Timothy
翻译：dzysteven 杨爱菜 JohnnyG  校对：油炸电风扇   木浅薰
时间轴：壬虚浪影 倩倩 biu
后期：斯人      总监：某羽
诉 讼 双 雄
第六季   第七集
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
你有不在场证明的证人
You had an alibi witness
然而你的公诉人却让她走掉了
and your public defender let her get away?
我一直都是这么说的啊
That's what I've been saying.
因为我一开始就跟你说了
I told you when I started this thing
我不会跟你串通的
I'm not going to collude.
我们这不是串通  这叫发现
We're not colluding. It's called discovery.
你赶快告诉我  凯文・米勒到底知道些什么
So, why don't you tell me what Kevin Miller knows?
凯文设计了一个交易软件
He developed the trading programs
萨特声称是靠那个软件获得了高额回报
that Sutter claims to use to get his superior returns.
所以你想要凯文作证
So you're looking to have Kevin testify
那个软件是狗屁  而萨特也是知情的
that software is bullshit, and Sutter knows it.
我发现长久以来不断努力
The thing that I worked so hard on
想到得到那自恋狂的认同的做法不过是谎言
to get that prick's approval was nothing but a lie.
-把这事告诉吉尔  -她早就知情了
- You told Jill and-- - She already knew.
她参与了
She was in on it.
哈维  老实告诉我包里到底放了什么
What the hell is in the bag, Harvey?
放着你需要用来保护案子
What you needed to keep this case going
而我一直不让你碰的东西
and I stopped you from getting.
所以痛快承认我们同一战线
So let's just admit that we're in this together
完成这件事
and get this thing done.
我要你现在保证
I want your word right now
你不会把我跟你说的告诉别人
that you won't tell anyone what I told you.
-凯文  拜托  -迈克  我说真的
- Kevin, please, you-- - Mike, I'm serious.
不许让别人
No one can ever know
知道我告诉你的事情
anything about what I told you.
法官还是决定
The judge decided to rule
撤销你的案子了
on your motion to dismiss after all.
这意味着我们没有时间了
Which means we're out of time.
我来问你要那个交易程序
I came here to ask for that trading program.
伦纳德・贝利的处决日期已经定下来了
Leonard Bailey's execution date has been set.
我不知道要怎么跟一个人说他马上就要死了
And I don't know how to tell a man that he's going to die.
你是谁
Who are you?
贝利先生  我是杰西卡・皮尔逊
Mr. Bailey, my name is Jessica Pearson.
我是你的首席辩护律师
And I'm lead counsel on your case.
你来这里
Well, you coming here,
肯定是有什么很重要的事
it must be about something important.
确实
It is.
伦纳德
Leonard,
你的处决日期已经定下来了
your execution date has been set.
什么时候
When?
-日期定下来了不代表  -什么时候
- Just because they've set the date doesn't-- - When?
三十天后
30 days.
伦纳德  我很抱歉
Leonard, I'm so sorry.
我不需要你的道歉
I don't need your sorry.
我想知道你会怎么处理这件事
I want to know what you're doing about this.
我们会提请一个延期动议
We're going to file a motion to delay.
我不在乎什么延期
I don't give a shit about delaying.
我是说
I mean,
你们打算如何救我出去
what are we doing to get me out?
我们正在努力
We're--we're working on it.
但是  伦纳德  现在很重要的一件事是
But I-I do think, Leonard, that it's really important
你得花些时间接受这个事情
that you take some time to process this.
我接受了十二年了
I've been processing for 12 years!
你说过你会找到玛利亚
You said that you were going to find Maria.
那请告诉我你为什么在这里
So tell me, what are you doing here
而不是在外面找人
instead of out there tracking her down?
伦纳德  我知道这很难
Leonard, I know that this is difficult, and--
贝利先生  瑞秋的意思是
Mr. Bailey, what Rachel means
我们下一步正是这么计划的
is that's exactly what we're going to do.
卡荷尔先生  你最好有个很好的理由
Mr. Cahill, you better have a compelling reason
阻止我通过斯佩克特先生的撤诉申请
why I shouldn't grant Mr. Specter a dismissal,
不然我马上就会通过
or this thing is going to be over before it gets started.
我有一个最有力的理由
Oh, I have the most compelling reason of all.
一份萨特先生交易软件的副本
A copy of Mr. Sutter's trading program.
胡说  他上周就在这试图
Bullshit. He was in here trying to subpoena
传唤这个软件
this thing last week
然后软件就这样出现在他手里了
and now it miraculously falls in his lap?
-你在暗示什么  -我在暗示
- What are you implying? - I'm implying
我不知道你做了什么  但肯定不是
I don't know what you did, but Santa sure as hell
圣诞老人昨晚放在你的树下的
didn't put that thing under your tree last night.
除非你能证明我做错了什么
Well, unless you have proof that I did something wrong,
否则你就闭嘴吧
you can shut the hell up.
好了  不要吵了
All right, that's enough.
假设这东西是合法取得的
Now assuming this thing is legitimate,
我能通过它了解到什么
what's it gonna show me?
您能了解到过去五年中萨特先生95%的交易
It's going to show you that it's responsible for 95%
都是通过这个软件完成的
of Mr. Sutter's trades over five years.
你是想帮我赢了这场官司吗
Are you trying to win this case for me
因为我一直辩护说
because my entire defense
我的客户是通过这个软件做的交易
is that my client makes his trades using that program.
-正是  -我关心的
- Exactly. - It's not the 95%
不是那95%  而是剩下的那5%
I'm concerned with, it's the other five.
他是靠那些交易赚取的那些高额利润
Those are the ones he made billions of dollars on.
他之所以能够那样做
The only way he could have done that
正是因为内幕交易
is by trading on inside information.
你的撤诉动议被否决了
Motion for dismissal denied.
先生们  我们要进行庭审
Gentlemen, we're going to trial.
但是卡荷尔先生  如果我发现
But Mr. Cahill, if it comes to light
这个东西是非法取得的
that you obtained this program illegally,
我不仅会撤销案子
not only am I going toss this case,
还会指控你恶意起诉
you're gonna be faced with a charge of malicious prosecution.
我们接下来要做的是
Here's what we're gonna do.
我不在乎我们接下来要做什么
I don't give a shit what we're gonna do.
我想知道他怎么得到的那个东西
I want to know where the hell he got that thing.
我不知道
I don't know,
但那不是我们需要解答的唯一问题
but that's not the only question we need to answer.
还有什么问题
What other question is there?
威廉  我不知道你有没有意识到
William, I don't know if you've noticed,
但你有个员工想要拉你下马
but you've got an employee that's looking to take you down
我们需要找出是谁
and we need to figure out who it is.
我们到底要怎样才能找出这个人
How exactly are we going to do that?
我们要开始
We're gonna start conducting interviews
和你每一个员工谈话
with every employee you have.
但在开始之前
But before we do that,
我要去确保肖恩・卡荷尔
I'm gonna make sure Sean Cahill
在证据交换阶段没有其他什么瞒着我们的了
isn't hiding anything else from us in discovery.
所以恕我失陪
So, if you'll excuse me,
我得独自去处理这件事了
I need to handle this myself.
你现在来找我干什么  哈维
What are you coming to me here for, Harvey,
萨特就在那里
Sutter's 30 feet away.
放心  他以为我是来确保
Relax. He thinks I'm making sure
你不会在证据交换阶段再耍什么花招的
that you didn't pull another fast one with discovery.
所以只要我俩看上去像是在吵架
So as long as it looks like we're arguing,
那就没问题
we're fine.
那不成问题  因为我有个消息告诉你
That's not gonna be a problem 'cause I got some news.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你一离开  她就立案了
Two seconds after you left, she put us on the docket.
五天之后就要上庭了
We go to trial in five days,
但如今我手上什么都没有
and right now I don't have shit.
你想让我说些什么呢  肖恩
What do you want me to say, Sean?
我已经利用刚刚那场戏
I'm already using what we did
来要求和他的员工们谈话了
to shake the trees with his employees.
那还不够
That's not good enough.
所以你必须回到监狱
So you need to go back to that prison
告诉迈克  他最好尽快给我套出点料来
and tell Mike that he better get me something and get it fast
因为我昨晚出卖灵魂
'cause I didn't sell my soul last night
可不是为了看着那混蛋逍遥法外的
to watch that bastard ride off into the sunset.
谢天谢地  你俩都在
Thank God you are both here.
法式甜甜圈  给女神一号
French cruller for goddess number one.
肉桂白糖甜甜圈  给女神二号
Cinnamon sugar for goddess number two.
尽管我很乐意接受一个美味的甜甜圈
While I do appreciated a tasty doughnut,
我还是想知道这是为了什么
I'd like to know what the occasion is.
路易买点心过来
There are exactly three reasons for Louis
只会有三个原因
to come bearing pastry.
埃斯特剪了个糟糕的发型
Esther got a bad haircut,
他找到人帮忙治疗他弯曲的拇指了
he found someone to fix his crooked thumb,
或者他想要寻求我们的建议
or he wants our advice.
我超级希望是拇指的事
I wish like hell it was the thumb,
但实际上我是来求建议的
but it's actually advice.
昨晚我和塔拉度过了很美好的一段时光
Last night, I had the most amazing time with Tara.
我知道你俩都在脑补一场棒棒的啪啪啪
I know you're both picturing it involved fantastic sex.
-没有  -一点都没有
- Nope. - Not a bit.
无论如何  塔拉和我周五晚上要约会
In any event, Tara and I have a date on Friday night,
我希望约会的结局是我俩的灵魂融为一体
and I'm hoping it ends with our souls merging as one.
-我退出  -什么  为什么
- And I'm out. - What? Why?
因为我是个专业的秘书  路易
Because I am a professional secretary, Louis.
我不是来帮你
I'm not here to help you play Hide the Litt
追某个妞儿的
with some strumpet.
她完全不懂我
She so doesn't get me.
知道吗  路易  她说的有道理
You know what, Louis? She has a point.
这话什么意思
What are you talking about?
为了追求这个我完全不认识的人
A lot of manpower has been devoted
你已经耗费了许多人力了
to your pursuit of this virtual stranger.
说到人力  我指的就是我宝贵的时间
And by manpower, I mean my precious time.
所以我觉得你是时候自己搞定了
So I think it's time that you took care of this yourself.
该死的
Goddamn it.
你觉得我要是搞得定的话我会找你们吗
Don't you think if I could have I would have?
我觉得  假如你不知道
What I think is, if you can't figure out
该如何和一个
how to have a simple date
已经答应了和你出去的女人约会的话
with a woman who's already agreed to go out with you,
那你也许从一开始
then maybe you don't deserve to go out with her
就不配约她出去
in the first place.
这个建议如何
How's that for advice?
哈维
Harvey.
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
什么叫我来这里干什么
What do you mean what am I doing here?
我需要知道你是否掌握了什么料
I need to know if you have anything yet.
-没有  -你在逗我吗
- I don't. - Are you kidding me?
他们两个人大吵之后
After the way those two guys got into it,
你居然告诉我凯文走出房间后
you're telling me Kevin didn't start talking
什么也没说吗
the second he left the room?
的确  他什么也没说
No. He didn't say a word.
我们必须让他吐露一些事情
Well, we need to get him to say something
这样才能把你弄出去
to get you out of here.
我知道  但我也不能按个按钮
Yeah, I know. But I can't just push a button
就让凯文背叛萨特啊
and get Kevin to turn on Sutter.
-不  你可以的  -什么意思
- Yes, you can. - What are you talking about?
你可以告诉他  他的算法被泄露给了卡荷尔
You can tell him his algorithm was leaked to Cahill.
什么时候的事
When the hell did that happen?
昨晚  我给他的
Last night, when I leaked it.
天呐  你们就这样串通一气了
Jesus Christ, so you're just out and out colluding now.
我别无选择
Look, I didn't have a choice.
除非卡荷尔拿出什么猛料
The judge was gonna toss this case
不然法官都打算放弃这个案子了
unless Cahill came up with a Hail Mary.
好吧  我尽力说服凯文
All right, I--I'll use it the best I can with Kevin.
但是  哈维  他很敏感
But, Harvey, he's sensitive.
这得花上一段时间
This is gonna take a little time.
问题就在这里  迈克  我们没时间了
That's the thing, Mike. We don't have time.
法官定下了开庭日期
The judge set a trial date.
如果你不能尽快为卡荷尔套出什么料
Which means if you don't get Cahill something soon,
接下来的两年你就得待在这里面了
you're gonna be sitting here for the next two years.
怎么了  瑞秋
What's going on, Rachel?
回来的路上你一句话都没说
You haven't said a word the entire ride back.
没什么
Nothing.
只不过是实际情况比我想象中还要难得多
Just a lot harder than I thought it would be.
你没想到他会发火
You didn't think he would be angry.
我没想到他会冲着我们发火
I didn't think that he'd be angry at us.
他不是在冲我们发火
Well, he wasn't angry at us.
只不过房间里没有其他人而已
There just wasn't anybody else in that room.
那现在怎么办
So now what?
现在我们努力解决这件事
Now we try to fix this damn thing.
你是说要找到玛利亚・戈麦斯
You mean by finding Maria Gomez.
我是说要推迟行刑
I mean by delaying this execution.
杰西卡  伦纳德说得对
Jessica, Leonard's right.
如果我们不能推翻死刑
What good does it do to delay the execution
推迟有什么意义
if we can't stop it from happening?
因为如果不推迟  我们就没有时间
Because if we don't, we don't have time
去找到玛利亚・戈麦斯
to find Maria Gomez.
我在想你昨晚跟我说的
I was thinking about what you told me last night
给吉尔弄豁免权的事
about getting Jill immunity.
迈克  我说过了  我不想谈这件事
Mike, I told you, I don't want to talk about this.
那你想谈谈如果萨特还是倒台了
Maybe you want to talk about what's going to happen to her
她会怎么样吗
if Sutter goes down anyway.
-不会的  -你怎么知道
- That's not gonna happen. - You don't know that.
我只知道如果我们之中
Yeah, well, I know what happens
有人出卖他会怎么样
if either one of us turns on him.
我们会落得身无分文
We won't have a penny to our name.
你开玩笑吧  你留在这儿他付你钱吗
Are you kidding me? Is he paying you to be in here?
听我说  我们拥有的一切都跟他有关
Listen to me, everything we have is tied to that man.
如果他坐牢了  我们会失去一切
And if he goes away, we lose it all.
我问的不是这个  他有没有承诺
That's not what I asked. Did he promise you money
只要你不出卖他  他就给你钱
if you kept quiet?
他当然承诺了
Of course he goddamn did.
等到我出去的那天  吉尔和我
And the day I get out of here, Jill and I are going to
会拿着那笔钱开始新的生活
take that money and start a new life.
你们也可以跟控方达成协议  马上开始新生活
Or you could both cut a deal and start a new life right now.
那会是一种什么样的生活
What kind of life is that gonna be?
因为我自己是白手起家
Because I come from nothing.
所以我不会让我的孩子过那样的生活
And I'm not gonna do that to my kids.
其实还有比白手起家更差的
Well, I'm telling you there are worse things you could be.
你怎么对我的生活这么感兴趣
Why are you so interested in my well being?
因为我是你的朋友  设身处地为你着想
Because I'm your friend and I was in your position.
我觉得你最好是把实话说出来
And I decided it was better to give it all up
而不是一直担惊受怕
than to keep looking over my shoulder
等着有一天真相大白
waiting for the ax to fall.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你知道我是诈骗犯  并且持续了多年对吧
You know I was a fraud, right? You know I did it for years.
你不知道的是
What you don't know is that I quit
我在被捕前二十分钟辞了职
20 minutes before I got arrested.
而那二十分钟是我人生最平和的时候
And it was 20 of the most peaceful minutes of my entire life.
好  但是看看你现在的下场
Yeah, well, look at what happened to you anyways.
-凯文  那不是  -够了
- Kevin, that's not the-- - That's enough.
我说过我不想谈这个  不想谈
I told you I'm done talking about it, and I'm done.
如果你真的是我的朋友
And if you're really my friend,
就再也别跟我提这件事
you won't ever bring this up to me again.
搞到《汉密尔顿》的后台座位
Get backstage seats to "Hamilton."
租到中央公园
Mm, rent out Central Park.
乘协和式客机去巴黎
Fly the Concorde to Paris.
不  等等  太蠢了
No, wait, that's stupid
因为现在已经没有协和式客机了
because they don't have the Concorde anymore.
我的天呐  就这个了
Holy shit, that's it.
找到现存最后的协和式客机
Find the last existing Concorde,
租下来  然后飞去巴黎
rent it, and fly that to Paris.
路易  不管你在做什么  我要你先放一放
Louis, whatever you're doing, I need you to put it down.
现在不行  哈维  我在计划
Not now, Harvey. I'm planning the ultimate date
跟我此生挚爱的终极约会
for the love of my life.
是迈克的事
This is for Mike.
好吧  你需要我做什么
All right, what do you need me to do?
这是近五年威廉・萨特
This is every big money trade
做的每一笔大额交易
William Sutter's made in the last five years.
我要你检查一遍  逆推一下
I need you to go through it, reverse engineer it,
找到所有内部交易的证据
and find any evidence you can of insider trading.
如果我有萨特的文件会容易很多
That would be a lot easier if I had access to Sutter's files.
我现在没办法给你那些
Well, I can't get that to you right now.
-为什么  -因为不能让他知道我们的动作
- Why not? - Because he can't know we're doing this.
好吧  哈维  上周你跟我说
Okay, Harvey, last week you told me
你是为了保护我
that you were protecting me
才什么都不告诉我
by not telling me what's going on.
别再保护我了
Stop protecting me,
到底是什么情况
and what the hell is going on?
我跟肖恩・卡荷尔做了笔交易
I cut a deal with Sean Cahill.
扳倒萨特  迈克出狱
Sutter goes down, Mike gets out.
-我的天呐  -我知道
- Holy shit. - I know.
别跟我说迈克还没搞到你要的东西
And don't tell me Mike still doesn't have anything for you.
对  他还没有  而还有五天就开庭了
No, he doesn't. And his trial starts in five days.
-那我最好赶紧开始  -谢谢你  路易
- Well, I better get on it. - Thank you, Louis.
迈克  怎么样了
Hey, Mike. How's it going?
你在这里做什么  加洛
What are you doing here, Gallo?
你知道  在外面的时候
You know, when I was on the outside,
我不是块头最大的  不是最强的
I wasn't the biggest, I wasn't the strongest,
甚至不是最聪明的
I wasn't even the smartest.
但大家让我管事  知道为什么吗
but they let me run things. You know why?
不知道  但我觉得你马上要告诉我了
No. I have a feeling you're about to tell me.
情况不对的时候我特别敏感
I had a knack for knowing when something didn't smell right.
你现在就不太对
Something doesn't smell right with you.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你要告诉我
You're gonna tell me
哈维今早没有来见你吗
Harvey didn't stop by this morning to see you.
-开始紧密监视我了吗  -当然了
- Tracking my every move now? - I sure as hell am.
你以为我会把我的自由全权交给你们吗
You think I'm gonna trust the two of you with my freedom?
哈维说了他会把你弄出去  就会说到做到
Harvey said that he'll get you out and he will.
那如果他已经试了但失败了呢
And what if he already tried and he can't?
没有这种事
That didn't happen.
是吗  让我们来想一下可能的情况
Yeah, well let me run a little scenario by you.
他提交了你要提交的文件  但是没有通过
He filed whatever you filed and it didn't fly.
然后他来告诉你这件事
Then he came to tell you that,
这样你们俩就能统一口径了
so the two of you would have your stories straight
从而一直操控着我
so you could string me along.
不是这么回事  加洛
That's not what happened, Gallo.
他是因为我的案子来找我
He came here to see me about my case.
跟你说吧  迈克
You want to know something, Mike?
我根本不在乎你的案子
I don't give a shit about your case.
所以你告诉哈维  他下次再来
So you tell Harvey next time he comes here,
最好带来点新进展
he better come with some progress.
因为我感觉很准
'Cause I've got that sense of smell.
你俩肯定在干脏事
And something in here stinks.
唐娜・鲍尔森的办公室  有何贵干
Donna Paulsen's office, how can I help you?
有一通来自丹伯里...
You have a call from Danbury...
我来付费
I'll accept the charges.
正在接通中  请勿挂断
Please hold while your call is being connected.
-唐娜  -还有一周才是我生日
- Donna. - My birthday's not for another week,
但还是谢谢你打来电话问候
but I appreciate the call.
你生日还有五个月零六天呢
Your birthday's not for another five months and six days
你明知道我记得很清楚
and you know I know that.
我也知道你到时肯定在场
And I also know that you'll be here
帮我跟大家一起庆生
helping me celebrate with everyone.
谢谢你  唐娜
Thanks, Donna.
你还好吧
You doing okay?
还能撑住
Yeah, I'm hanging in.
很好  你需要我帮什么忙
Good. Now what's the favor you were going to ask me?
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
因为你打给了我  没打给哈维
Because you called my line and not Harvey's,
并且我能感觉到我的朋友有求于我
and I know when my friend needs me.
说吧  想让我帮你干什么
So why don't you tell me how I can help?
你还记得有次你找人假扮我
Do you remember that time you impersonated someone for me
差点进了监狱吗
and almost went to prison?
有点印象
Rings a bell.
我想让你故技重施一次
I need you to do the exact same thing.
只不过这次  我找到了一种完全合法的方式
Only this time I found a way to make it totally legal.
让我先搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
你们想让我推迟他的行刑时间
You want me to delay this man's execution
理由就是他十二年前的那个主张
based on his own assertion from 12 years ago
有人能证明他不在场
that there's an alibi witness?
法官大人  我们知道
Your Honor, we understand
这不足以启动重审程序
that's not enough to reopen the case.
我们只想申请更多时间来找到那个证人
We're just asking for more time to locate the witness.
你们有十二年的时间去寻找证人
You've had 12 years to locate the witness.
更不用说就在行刑日期确定的当天
Not to mention that the day the execution is set
她们的委托人恰好就
is the day that their client just happened
突然想起还有个目击证人
to suddenly remember the witness in the first place.
他不是突然想起的
He didn't suddenly remember.
他十二年来一直都是这么跟别人说的
He's been saying it for 12 years.
并且他终于找到一个足够重视事实
And he finally found someone who cares enough about the truth
想帮他找到她的人
to help him find her.
好大的胆子
How dare you.
我重视事实
I care about the truth.
是我证明了他谋杀
And I convicted a murderer.
法官大人  这是对两名
Your Honor, this was a brutal murder
十六岁少年的血腥谋杀
of two 16-year-old children.
这两个孩子的家人今天也已到场
And the families of both of those children are here today
因为他们已经等待了十二年
because they've waited 12 years
想给这场噩梦画上句号
for their nightmare to finally end
没有任何法律上的理由让他们继续承受这样的折磨
and there is no legal reason to prolong their suffering.
法官大人
Your Honor,
您有权推迟伦纳德・贝利的行刑日期
you have the power to push Leonard Bailey's execution
只要您认为理由正当
if you see fit.
即使他只有1%的可能是清白的
Isn't it worth doing
这么做不也是值得的吗
if there's even a 1% chance that he is innocent?
你们有一周时间来找到证人
You have one week to find a witness.
一周后  你们就不能再申请重审
After that, you cannot move to reopen his trial
他的行刑日期就不会再变了
and his execution date is set in stone.
你在这  我找了你一上午
There you are. I've been looking for you all morning.
我之前在忙正事  路易
I had something important to do, Louis.
这会也要忙点别的工作
And now I have actual work to catch up on,
所以现在不能跟你聊你约会的事
so I can't really talk to you about your date right now.
不  不  不是约会的事
No, no. It's not about my date.
是哈维案子的事
It's about Harvey's case.
我知道跟迈克有关
I know it's for Mike.
怎么了
What is it?
哈维想让我逆推萨特的那些交易
Harvey wants me to reverse engineer Sutter's trades,
但没有交易数据库  我就做不到
but I can't do that without access to a trading database.
并且我们不能向证监会求助
And we can't ask the SEC
因为他们应该是我们的对手
because they're supposed to be on the other side.
那你为什么来找我了
So why are you coming to me?
因为斯图・二货脸・布齐尼有数据库
Because Stu "Dickface" Buzzini has a database.
然而他却是这世上最不愿意帮你的人
And he's the last person in the world who would help you.
求你了  唐娜  如果有别的办法
Donna, please, I would not be coming to you
我就不会来找你了
if there was another way,
我熬了一夜都没想出别的办法
but I have been up all night and there is no other way.
我会搞定的  路易
I'll take care of it, Louis.
-给  -这是什么
- Here. - What's this?
-我的人  -你的人
- That's my guy. - Your guy?
我的私家侦探
My private investigator.
名片上怎么没写
Why doesn't it say it on the card?
因为这么优秀的人用不着上电话簿
Because a guy that good isn't in the phone book.
瑞秋  达到某种层次后
Listen, Rachel, when you get to a certain level,
每个人都有自己的人
everybody has their person.
哈维有凡妮莎  我有卡特
Harvey has Vanessa, I have Carter.
现在也是我的了
And now I do too.
不  这次借你是因为我们时间不多了
No, you have him for this because we don't have time.
下一次  你去找你自己的人
After that, you get your own guy.
我不明白
I don't understand,
为什么不能跟你共用一个
why can't I use your guy too?
那还怎么能称得上是我的人
Because then he wouldn't be my guy.
有什么能为你效劳的  红发女郎
What can I do for you, Red?
我正忙着呢
I'm in the middle of something.
你可以把眼睛从屏幕上挪开两秒钟
You can turn away from that screen for two seconds
用绅士的方式自我介绍一下
and introduce yourself to me like a gentleman.
为什么你们办公室每次有人来找我
Why is it anytime someone from your office comes to me,
都要评论我的礼仪
they've always got some kind of comment on my manners?
也许这个问题你该问自己
Maybe that's a question you should be asking yourself.
但我没时间细究你为什么永远不会自己想
But I don't have time to delve into why you'll never do that
因为我需要你让路易・利特
because I need you to give Louis Litt access
查看你的整个证券数据库
to your entire securities database.
我不知道你是谁
Listen to me, I don't know who the hell you are,
但我为什么要为你这么做
but why exactly am I going to do that for you?
因为你这么做  我就欠你一个人情
Because when you do, I'll owe you one,
如果你还不知道那我告诉你
and if you don't know it already,
我欠你一次比别人五十次都好用
that's like anyone else owing you 50.
我不信
I don't buy it.
那你可以问问你在美林证券的朋友拉里
Then why don't you call your friend Larry at Merrill Lynch
或者摩根史坦利投资的肯尼
or Kenny at Morgan Stanley
或者霍华德・杰夫  你知道他在哪的
or Howard Jaffe from you know where?
你怎么知道霍华德的事的
How the hell do you know about Howard?
他们的事我都知道
I know about all of them.
这是我的专长
Because it's what I do.
好吧  你要什么都行
Okay, uh, you can have whatever you want.
很好  因为你质疑我的能力
Good. And sense you questioned my abilities,
所以你不但要给路易提供数据库
you're not only gonna give Louis that database,
还要在你的余生中  永远给他
you're going to treat him with the respect he deserves
应有的尊重
for the rest of your life.
我就没有欺负过他
I never did anything wrong to him.
如果你真信这句话
And if you think that's true,
那你真的需要好好照照镜子了
then you need to take a good look in the mirror
因为你玷污了他的大办公室和马克杯
because you violated his bullpen and his mugs.
而除了和我的友谊外
And with the exception of my friendship,
那是他生命中最重要的两个东西
those are the two most important things in his entire life.
你的表情告诉我
I can see by that look on your face
你终于在想我到底是谁了
you're wondering who I am after all.
我给你省点麻烦
Let me save you the trouble.
我是唐娜  我很厉害
I'm Donna, and I'm awesome.
抱歉  我想是我走错房间了
Excuse me. I think I'm in the wrong room.
不  没走错
No, you're not.
凯文呢
Where's Kevin?
我是他室友
I'm his cell mate
他在哪不是眼下最重要的问题
and where he is isn't important right now.
我接到了狱警的电话
I got a phone call from a guard
说我丈夫要见我
saying that my husband wanted to see me,
我要知道到底是怎么回事
and I want to know what's going on.
不  你是接到了一个说来自
No, you got a phone call from someone saying
丹伯里监狱的电话
they were calling from Danbury,
那通电话也确实是这里打出的
which is exactly where that call was made.
那我现在就要离开这个地方
And now it's exactly where I'm headed out of.
我知道你在帮你父亲进行非法交易
I know you're helping your father make illegal trades.
-什么  -你可以否认
- What? - You can go ahead and deny it,
但凯文都告诉我了
but Kevin told me everything.
你想怎样
What do you want?
我想帮你
I want to help you.
我不信
Well, I don't believe you.
我不在乎你信不信
I don't care if you believe it or not,
但你只有一个短暂的机会  可以向证监会自首
but you have a small window to come clean with the SEC
以免牢狱之灾
and save yourself.
虽然这不关你的事
Not that it's any of your business,
但我告诉你我不会背叛我父亲
but I would never turn on my own father.
真不幸  因为如果你不这么做
That's too bad because if you don't,
那你们俩都要进监狱
you're both gonna end up behind bars.
这事对你有什么好处
What exactly is in this for you?
对我没什么好处
There's nothing in it for me
我只是因为在乎凯文
besides that fact that I care about Kevin.
我曾为哈维・斯佩克特工作
Listen to me, I used to work for Harvey Specter,
他是你父亲的律师
your father's lawyer.
要是他知道我这么做了
If he found out that I was doing this,
肯定要杀了我
he would kill me.
要是我把这事告诉我父亲呢
And what if I tell my father about all this?
你不会的
You're not gonna do that.
因为凯文已经告诉我
Because Kevin already told me
你们打算拿着威廉的钱离开
that you guys are planning to go away on William's dime,
要是你父亲发现凯文告诉了我
so if your father finds out that Kevin's been talking to me,
就不会给你们钱了
that dime's gonna go away.
我说了  我走错房间了
Like I said, I'm in the wrong room.
坐吧  布莱恩
Have a seat, Bryan.
我问几个问题
I just have a few questions,
然后你就可以走了
and then you can be on your way.
到底是要问什么
What exactly is this about?
-你还不知道  -不知道
- You don't know? - No.
我问了十个人谁也不告诉我什么
I talked to ten people here and no one will tell me a thing
只是说不好对付
except that this isn't going to be easy.
因为有人匿名
That's because the SEC
向证监会递交了威廉・萨特的交易软件
got an anonymous copy of William Sutter's trading program,
我要知道是哪个混蛋泄露的
and I want to find the son of a bitch who leaked it.
我可以告诉你不是我
Well, I can tell you it wasn't me.
前面那十个白痴也是这么说的
Which is exactly what those ten other clowns just said.
我也把给他们的答案再给你
And I'll tell you what I told them,
那东西不是从天上掉进证监会的
it didn't magically appear on their doorstep.
我不管他们是怎么拿到的
I don't care how they got it.
如果你只有这一个问题
And if that's your only question,
那我要回去工作了
I need to get back to work.
我说让你走  你才能走
You'll leave when I say you can leave.
你说什么
What did you say?
我说让你给我坐下
I said sit the hell down.
你当了五年副经理
You've been a VP for five years,
但是去年夏天你见过高盛和摩根的人
but you took meetings at Goldman and Morgan last summer.
这件事我告诉过萨特先生
Which I disclosed to Mr. Sutter.
我不管  你没得到工作
I don't care. You didn't get those jobs
是因为他们不要你
because they didn't want you.
你现在很生气  因为那些级别比你低的人
And now you're pissed off the people under you
却能拿到你两倍的工资
are making twice your salary,
所以你跑去证监会告密
so you went running to the SEC.
我已经说了我没有
I already told you I didn't do that.
三天前的晚上你在哪
Where were you three nights ago?
在吃饭  你可以查
I was at dinner. You can check.
是和你的老朋友亨利・里瑟吗
Was it with your old buddy, Henry Reese,
而他恰巧和五名证监会的律师
who just happens to play rec-league basketball
一起打篮球联赛
with five SEC lawyers?
我已经半年没见过亨利了
I haven't seen Henry in six months,
而且我也有点受够了你的审问了
and I'm getting a little sick and tired of this interrogation.
我也受够了你这种
Well, I'm getting sick and tired of assholes like you
不把这件事当真的混蛋了
not taking this thing seriously.
什么  我没说过我不当真
What? I didn't say I wasn't taking it seriously.
对  我不在乎你说过什么
Yeah, I don't give a shit what you said.
我在乎的是
I give a shit that
你要开始认真听我说的话
you start listening to what I'm goddamn telling you
因为当证监会让你出庭作证的时候
because when the SEC gets you on the stand,
他们会用放大镜把你的生活翻个底朝天
they're going to go through your life with a fine tooth comb,
如果你有任何隐瞒
and if you got something to hide,
他们都会查出来
they're gonna find it.
-对不起  -很好
- I'm sorry. - Good.
从我眼前消失  叫下一个混蛋进来
Get the hell out of my sight and send the next asshole in.
路易  我能跟你说句话吗
Louis, can I talk to you for a minute?
如果你带来了我想要的东西的话
Only if you're here to bring me what I need.
我带了
I am.
这个小东西能让你直接链接到我们的主机
That baby will link you directly to our mainframe.
如果你还需要其他东西  来找我
You need anything else, you come to me.
-谢谢你  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
还没完
But that's not all.
我还带了另一个小礼物
I also brought a little something
来弥补我们的关系
to make things right between us.
我自作主张更新了设计
I took the liberty of updating the design.
希望你喜欢
I hope you like it.
我爱死它了
I love it.
很好  因为档案室还有六打杯子呢
Good. 'Cause there's six dozen more in the file room.
重新开始  兄弟
Fresh start, bro?
重新开始
Fresh start.
斯图
Hey, Stu.
唐娜说了什么让你做出此番举动的
What exactly did Donna say to get you to do all this?
她只是给我立了面镜子
She just held up a mirror.
事实上  在待人处事方面听取他人的意见
And the truth is, it never hurts to get a second opinion
并不是件坏事
on how you treat other people.
杰西卡  你给我卡特的名片是对的
Jessica, you were right to give me Carter.
没有他我绝对发现不了
I never would have found out
玛利亚・戈麦斯的情况
what happened to Maria Gomez without him.
说说看
Let's have it.
她2008年在新泽西提交了更改名字的文件
She filed for a name change in New Jersey in 2008.
她的新名字叫什么
What's her new name?
这就是问题所在
That's just it.
卡特找不到她的新名字
Carter couldn't get it.
他找不到的唯一原因
The only reason he couldn't get it
是州政府考虑到她的安全拒绝任何人
is if the state is denying access to those records
-接触这份记录  -没错
- for her own safety. - Exactly.
她提交了大量对他丈夫的限制令
She filed numerous restraining orders against her ex-husband,
现在她的文件在接下来两年里都将是保密的
and now her records are sealed for the next two years.
好吧  让我找找看
All right. I'll see if there's someone
纽瓦克地检办公室有没有人能帮忙
at the Newark DA's office who can help us.
如果我没有  也许哈维能有认识的人
If not, maybe Harvey knows someone.
我认识一个
I know someone.
我父亲和吉米・罗杰斯一起上的法学院
My father went to law school with Jim Rogers,
他是纽瓦克的地检官
the Newark District Attorney.
你不想去找你父亲
And you don't want to go to your father
是因为你不想找他帮忙
because you don't want to ask him for a favor.
我不想让他一直我当成
I don't want him to keep seeing me as
一个总是需要帮助的小姑娘
some little girl who's always asking for help with something.
瑞秋  身为律师意味着你需要寻求他人帮助
Rachel, being a lawyer means you have to ask people for help,
不论他们是谁
no matter who they are,
也就是说如果你想让你父亲知道
which means if you want to let your father know
你不再是一个小姑娘了
that you're not a little girl anymore,
那你要让他知道你不怕求他帮忙
then show him you're not afraid to ask him for a favor.
请坐  詹妮弗
Have a seat, Jennifer.
我就问几个问题
I just have a few questions,
你就可以走了
then you can be on your way.
我想我还是站着吧
I think I'll stand.
-你不是詹妮弗  -对  我不是
- You're not Jennifer. - No, I'm not.
在告诉我你到底打的什么算盘之前
I'm not sending another person in here
我不会让任何人进来的
until you tell me what the hell you're doing.
我在做我之前说过要做的事情
I'm doing what I said I was gonna do.
你说你要试探军情
You said you would shake the trees,
而不是动摇军心
not burn down the whole forest.
-听我说  -不  你听我说
- Listen to me-- - No, you listen to me.
你是在赶走我的手下  这件事到此为止
You're driving my people away, and that ends now.
威廉  你不懂
William, I don't think you understand,
那个泄露机密的贱人越早停止
the sooner the son of a bitch who leaked this thing
和他们的合作
stops helping them,
对我们越有利
the better for us.
你凭什么认为这个人
What makes you think whoever it is
会停止和他们的合作
is gonna stop helping them?
他是匿名递交的材料
Look, they handed it in anonymously,
也就是说不管这个混蛋是谁
which means whoever this asshole is,
这件事告诉我们的是  他是个胆小鬼
the one thing they showed us is, he's a coward.
阻止胆小鬼的唯一办法
And the only way to stop a coward
就是吓死他们
is to scare the shit out of them.
如果赢意味着失去我所有的员工
Well, if winning my case means losing all my employees,
那这整件事就算了吧
then forget about the whole thing.
-威廉  我们不能停止...  -够了
- William, we can't stop-- - That's enough.
你现在不应该是寻找一个
Instead of looking for someone
已经发生的事实的罪魁祸首
who did something they already did,
而应该是回去为我的辩护做准备
you're gonna get back to preparing my defense.
下次我见到你
The next time I see you,
你最好给我一个前所未有的最有力的
you'd better be giving the most kick-ass opening statement
开庭陈诉
the world's ever seen.
你到底干了什么
What the hell did you do?
凯文  听我解释
All right, Kevin, let me explain.
解释什么  冒充我叫我妻子
Explain what? That you called my wife in here
来这里吗
pretending to be me?
先听我说  我...
Just listen to me, I'm--
我不能相信你
You know, I can't believe you, man.
我叫你不要把我们说过的话告诉任何人
I told you not to tell anyone what we talked about.
我也并没有告诉其他人啊
And I didn't tell anyone who didn't already know.
我才不管
And I don't give a shit
因为这不关你他妈一点事
because this is none of your goddamn business.
是  但我让它变成了我的事
Yeah, well, I made it my goddamn business
因为你现在面前正有一辆货车向你驶来
because there is a freight train headed right at you,
如果我不做点什么阻止它
and if I didn't do everything I could to stop it,
我良心过不去
I wouldn't be able to live with myself.
但你并没有阻止它
Yeah, well, you didn't stop it.
而是直接用它来破坏我的婚姻
You slammed it right into my marriage
因为我和吉尔
because Jill and I,
自打我进监狱的那一晚开始
we haven't fought like we just did
就没有像刚才那样大吵过
since the night that landed me in here,
所以从现在开始
so from now on,
带起你的好心好意给我滚
take your goddamn good intentions and go to hell.
你知道吗  你应该感谢我
You know what? You should be thanking me.
感谢你什么  破坏我的人生吗
Thanking you for what? Screwing up my life?
提醒你一句  你的人生已经被破坏了
In case you haven't noticed, your life is already screwed up.
你替人顶罪进了这里
You're in here because of some other guy's crime,
如果那个人被抓  你们会一起在监狱度过余生
and if he gets caught, you're gonna be in here together.
然后那些他承诺要给你的
And then all of that fictional money
虚拟的金钱
that he's dangling in front of you
都会打水漂
isn't gonna be there anymore.
现在我懂你为什么费心做这些事了
Now I get why you're going through all this trouble.
你后悔为别人做了交易
You regret that you took a deal for someone,
他现在逍遥法外而你却在蹲监狱
and he's out there while you're in here.
我并不后悔
Well, I don't.
因为我不是为了那个杂种进了监狱
Because I didn't take this deal for that son of a bitch,
我进来是为了我很爱的妻子
I took it for my wife, who I love,
如果你再未经我的允许找她
and if you ever contact her again without my blessing,
我对天发誓我会痛扁你
I swear to God I will beat the shit out of you.
唐娜  路易在哪
Donna, where the hell is Louis?
他在给你干活
He's working on what you wanted.
有事  去把他找来
Well, find him because I need him.
哈利  有什么问题吗
Harvey, what's the matter?
问题是  我在萨特的公司花了一整天
What's the matter is, I just spent the whole day at Sutter's
想要找到是谁跟他共谋了
trying to flush out whoever's in on this with him,
但一无所获
and I got nowhere.
我不懂  这肯定需要时间的
I don't understand. It's gonna take time.
这才过了一天
This was only one day.
没错  但萨特不让我这么做了
Which would be true, except Sutter shut me down
所以我没有机会去找了
and I don't have another day.
我也说了  我在那里时
And like I said, while I was there,
并没有在任何人的脸上看到负罪的表情
I didn't see a guilty look on a single person's face.
因为你要找的那个人
Because the person you're looking for
并不为威廉・萨特工作
doesn't work for William Sutter.
我去  你找到他了吗
Holy shit. You found him?
我不仅找到了他  我还有证据
I didn't just find him. I got backup.
萨特所交易的这些资金的一个共同点是
The one commonality on all the trades Sutter made money on
他们是通过和一个投资银行
was they preceded some sort of transaction
进行这些交易的
involving an investment bank.
这我知道  但是有20个不同的银行
I know that, but there were 50 different trades
牵涉了50桩不同的交易
with 20 different banks.
是20个不同的代理银行
20 different agent banks.
银行还有其他种类吗
What the hell other kind of bank is there?
用来给你第二意见的银行
The kind of bank you hire to give you a second opinion.
我去  咨询银行
Holy shit, the consulting banks.
正是  而且它们
Exactly, which, by the way,
并不要求被公开
are not required to be disclosed.
有多少咨询银行
How many different banks were they?
就一个  而主管这个银行咨询部的人
Just one. And that bank's consulting division
他在华尔街第一份工作的老板
happens to be run by a man whose first job on Wall Street
正是威廉・萨特
was working for William Sutter.
抱歉又来打扰你  肖恩
Sorry to be showing up at your place again, Sean,
但是这耽搁不得
but this can't wait.
没事  哈维  我现在心情正好
That's okay, Harvey. You caught me in a good mood.
我会让你的心情更好
Well, I'm about to make it better
因为我们已经找到
because we found the guy
那个向萨特提供信息的人了
who's been feeding Sutter his information.
-他是...  -菲利普・亚伦  我知道
- His name is-- - Phillip Allen, I know.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
两个小时前他来找我签协议
He came by to cut a deal two hours ago,
我跟他签了
so I gave him one.
-不  你没有  -有什么问题吗
- No, you goddamn didn't. - What's your problem?
问题是  他来找你是因为我
My problem is, I drove him to you.
那又怎样  这事儿就快结束了  哈维
So what? We're at the finish line, Harvey.
这就是我们一直想要的结果
This is what we've been after the whole time.
这是你一直想要的结果
This is what you've been after this whole time.
我想要的结果是救出迈克
What I've been after is getting Mike out,
如果你觉得你能够就这样逃避交易
so if you think you can weasel out of this deal after--
哈维  冷静
Harvey, relax.
就证监会而言
As far as the SEC is concerned,
迈克直接指向那位证人
Mike led directly to the witness.
这将让那个该死的混蛋的余生
That's going to put that piece of shit away
都在监狱中悲惨的度过
for the rest of his miserable life.
所以迈克的协议依然有效吗
So Mike's deal is still intact?
坚如磐石
Rock solid.
我们逮到他了  哈维
We got him, Harvey.
最终还是好人赢了
The good guys won.
那么我猜你下次见到我
Then I guess the next time you see me,
我得装作对你没有告知我们
I'm gonna be pretending to be outraged
你有新证人这件事感到愤怒和震惊了
that you hadn't notified us of your new witness.
而我会对不管你扯的什么淡
And I'll be pretending to be outraged
也都装作愤怒和震惊
at whatever bullshit you're trying to pull.
好吧  我尽量试着不弄得太夸张
Well, I'll try not to be too outrageous.
就这么办吧
You do that.
-谢谢  肖恩  -不客气  哈维
- Thanks, Sean. - You're welcome, Harvey.
瑞秋
Rachel.
是我记错了吗
Did I mess something up?
我不记得我们今晚有约啊
I didn't think we had plans tonight.
我不是因为和你有约才过来的
I'm not here for plans.
那你过来是要做什么
Then what are you here for?
我有个案子需要你帮忙
I need your help with a case.
你不是真的要叫我帮我的对手吧
You're not seriously asking me to help my rival firm, are you?
不  不是商业案件
No, it's not corporate.
是无罪计划的案子
This is from the Innocence Project
从什么时候开始杰西卡・皮尔逊
And since when did Jessica Pearson
会接无罪计划的案子了
take on an Innocence Project case?
从我请求她这么做开始
Since I asked her to.
真棒  瑞秋  我为你感到骄傲
Well, that's great, Rachel. I'm proud of you.
你需要我帮什么忙
What do you need?
在新泽西州有一条隐私权法令
There's a privacy statute in the state of New Jersey
阻碍了我去找一位目击证人
that's preventing me from finding a witness.
而吉米・罗杰斯是不会接你的电话的
And Jim Rogers won't take a call from you,
但他会接我的
but he will from me.
完全正确  如果你帮我这一次
Exactly. And if you do this for me,
我就欠你一份情
I will owe you one.
瑞秋  你是我女儿  你永远不欠我的
Rachel, you're my daughter. You'll never owe me one.
我不是以你女儿的身份来的
Mm-mm. I'm not here as your daughter.
我是以一位律师的身份来的
I'm here as a lawyer.
那就不要忘了这一点
Then don't forget this.
因为有一天  我会找你帮忙的
Because someday, I'm gonna come calling.
迈克  坐
Mike, sit down.
我希望你大老远跑来
I hope you didn't come all the way down here
不是过来告诉我时间不多了
just to tell me that we're running out of time,
因为这一点我已经知道了
'cause I already know that.
并不是  我来是想告诉你我们逮到那家伙了
I didn't. I came here to tell you that we got the guy.
-谁  -那个一直给萨特提供
- What guy? - The guy who's been feeding
内幕消息的人  我把他逼去找卡荷尔了
inside information to Sutter, and I drove him to Cahill,
也就是意味着你要出狱了
which means you're getting out.
迈克  你听到我说的话了吗  你要出狱了
Mike, did you hear me? You're getting out.
不  我  我知道  我
No, I-I know. I...
听着  问题是如果你要给萨特定罪
Look, the problem is that if you're gonna get Sutter,
就同样会牵连到凯文的妻子
you're also gonna get Kevin's wife.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
凯文跟我说他一直不接受交易的原因
Kevin told me that the reason he never cut a deal
就是因为她妻子也牵连其中
was because his wife was in on it.
你跟我开玩笑吗  你一直把这件事自己瞒着
Are you kidding me? You've been keeping this to yourself?
我没有只是自己瞒着
I haven't just been keeping it to myself.
我也在试图说服凯文和吉尔坦白一切
I also tried to convince Kevin and Jill to both come clean.
他们俩  你去找她了吗
Both of them? You went to her?
-哈维  听我说  -不  你听我说
- Harvey, listen to me-- - No, you listen to me.
我不在乎你的良心在告诉你该怎么做
I don't give a shit what your conscience is telling you.
我们逮到这家伙了  我们要把他拿下
We got the guy. We're gonna take him down.
那意味着你可以出狱了
That means you get out.
我知道  我也很想这样
I know that, and I love that.
但我需要你去说服卡荷尔
But all I need you to do is convince Cahill
也跟吉尔做个交易
to cut Jill a deal too.
我觉得你没搞清楚
I don't think you understand.
这家伙自首了
This guy came forward.
他得到了这笔交易
He's the guy that gets the deal,
你也得到了这笔交易
and you're the guy that gets the deal.
-没有第三笔交易了  -哈维  拜托
- There's no third deal. - Harvey, please.
我背叛这个男人的事已经做得够多了
I've betrayed this man enough.
我需要你去说服卡荷尔一个证人可以搞定案子
I need you to convince Cahill that one person makes a case,
但两个证人能让他胜券在握
but two people is a slam dunk.
好吧  迈克  我去说服卡荷尔
Okay, Mike. I'll make it happen.
路易  有空吗
Louis? Do you have a second?
实际上  我没空  唐娜  因为我今晚
Actually, I don't, Donna, because I'm going
即将要去赴我人生中最重要的约会
on the most important date of my life tonight,
但我却完全不知道要带她去哪
and I have no idea where I'm taking her.
是的  你知道
Yes, you do.
从来没听过这个地方
Never heard of this place.
那是因为这是一家在那里已经开了
That's because it's an intimate restaurant
50年却没什么人知道的私密餐厅
that's been there 50 years and no one knows about it.
这让其作为一个去了解你认为可能
Which makes it the perfect place to get to know someone
会爱上的那个人的约会场所来说再好不过了
you think you might be falling in love with.
唐娜  我要震撼到她
Donna, I need to blow her away.
不  路易  你得让她去了解你
No, Louis, you need to let her get to know you
然后让命运决定接下来的一切
and let fate take care of the rest.
如果我不够好呢
What if I'm not good enough?
你足够好了
You are good enough.
我以为你太忙没时间帮忙
Hey, I thought you were too busy to help.
事实上  你叫我帮忙的时候
The truth is, when you asked me for help,
那个早晨我心情不好  不愿意去
it wasn't a great morning for me to be thinking
思考恋爱的事
about that kind of thing.
我不大明白
I don't understand.
我过去几个月一直在和某人交往
I've been seeing someone for the last few months,
我们分手了
and we broke up.
把那个混账的名字告诉我
Tell me the son of a bitch's name right now
本周结束之前我就把他的账户给冻结了
and I'm gonna freeze his assets by the end of the week.
他叫米歇尔  你没必要这么做
His name is Mitchell, and you don't have to do that.
有必要  唐娜  你是我最重要的人
Yes, I do, Donna. You're everything to me,
那个混账完全不知道自己多大福气...
and that asshole has no idea what he's got--
是我提出分手的  路易
It was my decision, Louis.
那你怎么这么伤心
Well then, why were you so upset?
这道理和你跟希拉的关系是一样的啊
It's the same thing it was with you and Sheila.
尽管你是先提出分手的人
Just because you were the one to break it off with her
也不意味着你不会伤心
doesn't mean that your heart wasn't still broken.
我爱你  唐娜
I love you, Donna.
我也爱你  路易
I love you too, Louis.
先生  有什么能帮您的吗
Sir, may I help you?
有  你带我去见杰西卡・皮尔逊
Yes, you can direct me to Jessica Pearson.
皮尔逊女士晚上不在这里
Ms. Pearson's gone for the evening,
我能替你转达消息
but I can take down your information
明天早上她就会回复你了
and she'll get back to you in the morning.
你不用转达任何消息
You're not taking anything down.
我需要立刻跟人对上话
I need to speak with someone now.
有事你可以对我说  福雷斯特先生
You can speak with me, Mr. Forrest.
我想你来这是要说伦纳德・贝利的事
I assume you're here to talk about Leonard Bailey.
我是来给你看这个的
I'm here to show you this.
这是那个男人对我女儿所犯下的罪行
This is what that man did to my daughter.
福雷斯特先生  我知道你很难过
Mr. Forrest, I know that this must be incredibly difficult.
也许你不这么想
And it may not seem that way to you,
但我是在为你女儿寻求公正的判决
but I am seeking justice for your daughter.
只有那个禽兽被判死刑才是最公正的判决
We got justice when that animal was sentenced to death,
别跟我说这样做是为了她
so don't you try to tell me you're doing this for her.
我这样做是为了所有人
I'm doing this for everyone.
这个案子曾被严重地错误处理了
The case was grossly mishandled.
-这不是你能决定的  -说的没错  先生
- That's not for you to decide. - You're right, sir.
-这是陪审团该决定的  -陪审团也判过了
- It's for a jury to decide. - A jury did decide!
他们当时并未看到所有真相
And they weren't presented with all of the facts.
真相就是他杀了我女儿
The facts are he killed my girl!
福雷斯特先生  我很同情你
Mr. Forrest, I'm so sorry for your loss.
但我发自内心地相信伦纳德・贝利是无辜的
But I believe in my heart that Leonard Bailey is innocent.
而我要确保
And I'm going to make sure
他能得到自己从未有过的公正判决
that he gets the fair trial that he never had.
方法就是找些瘾君子来做证人吗
By tracking down some junkie witness?
无论她是不是瘾君子
Drug user or not,
玛利亚・戈麦斯以前都没有机会说出证词
Maria Gomez never had a chance to be heard.
如果你不介意的话  我得回办公室了
If you'll excuse me, I need to go to my office.
我不会离开的
I'm not going anywhere!
除非你意识到如果你真的同情我
Not until you understand that if you are sorry for me,
当初就不会接这个案子
you wouldn't have taken this case on in the first place
不会为了名声而接这个案子
instead of using it to make a name for yourself.
够了
That's enough.
你该说的都说完了
You said everything you needed to say,
请你马上离开这里
now walk yourself out of here
不然我就叫保安来了
before I have security remove you.
你没事吧
You all right?
会没事的  谢谢你  格雷琴
I will be. Thank you, Gretchen.
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
没什么好谈的
There's nothing to talk about.
-我有  -好吧  随你谈
- There is for me. - All right then, go ahead.
反正也没用
It won't make any difference
因为我已经准备换牢房了
'cause I already put in for a transfer.
-你要搬走了吗  -没错
- You're moving to another cell? - Yeah, I am.
所以无论你说了什么
So whatever it is you're gonna say,
我都会假装你说完了  并且忘光
let's just pretend you said it, and I let it go,
之后咱们各走各道互不相见  可以吗
and we move in our separate directions, okay?
不  我没法这么做
No, I can't do that.
-为什么  -因为你说得对
- Why not? - Because you were right.
我气自己接受协议来救别人
I am pissed that I took a deal to save other people.
如今我要在牢里呆上两年
And now I'm sitting in here for two goddamn years
他们却逍遥自在
while they're out there.
如果你还是想搬走  我能理解
If you still want to transfer cells,I get it.
我不会心存芥蒂的
I won't hold any hard feelings.
我想让你知道  伤害你和吉尔
I want you to know that hurting you and Jill
是我最不想做的事情
is the last thing that I wanted to do.
我今晚会去看电影
I'm gonna head to movie night.
希望能在那里见到你
I hope to see you there.
杰西卡  你不是回家过夜了吗
Jessica, I thought you went home for the night.
我又回来了
I came back.
听说受害者父亲来找你麻烦了
I heard you had some trouble with the victim's father.
-格雷琴跟你说了  -没错
- Gretchen told you. - Yes, she did.
还好她跟我说了
And I'm glad she did.
-他有威胁你吗  -没
- Did he threaten you? - No.
我当初应该先跟你说
I guess I should have told you.
人们在经历悲痛的时候往往不太理智
People don't always act rationally when they're suffering.
他们想找人来怪罪
They look for someone to blame.
-于是就怪罪在我身上  -没错
- Yeah, well, he's blaming me. - Yes, he is.
-他错了  -我知道
- And he's wrong. - I know.
这事要理解起来很容易
And that's an easy thing to understand.
但要忍受却很难
But a harder thing to endure.
好吧  一想到有你支持我
Well, it just got a little bit easier
我感觉好受了一点
knowing that you're in it with me.
我们去喝杯酒吧
Let's go get a drink.
发生了这么多事  一杯可不够我喝的
After what happened before, I think I might have two.
-路易  这个地方...  -太静了是不是
- Louis, this place is...  - It's too quiet in here,isn't it?
椅子上还没垫子
The seats aren't padded.
-你讨厌这里  我就知道  -不  这里很完美
- And you hate it, I know it. - No, Louis, it's perfect.
这里完全符合我的期望
It's exactly what I'd hoped for.
我想让你知道我有多在乎你
Well, I wanted to show you how much you mean to me.
-路易...  -我明白
- Louis... - I get it.
-你对我没感觉  -不是那样的
- You don't feel the same way. - It's not that.
我有些事告诉你
I have something to tell you,
我不知该从何说起
and I didn't know how to bring it up.
也不知该什么时候说
Or even when,
但你表现的这么浪漫
but you made such a romantic gesture
让我觉得不说都对不起你
that it--it feels wrong not to tell you about it.
说什么
What is it?
我有男朋友并且他每年一半时间住在洛杉矶
I have a boyfriend who lives in Los Angeles six months of the year.
我们非常看重彼此
We care about each other deeply,
但是异地恋对我们的感情影响很大
but living across the country takes its toll.
所以我们约好了
So we came up with an arrangement
彼此可以和其他人约会
where we allow each other to see other people.
你是说你想同时和我们两个交往
You're saying you want to date both of us?
我知道这听起来很疯狂
I know it sounds crazy.
其实  我从来都没有真正履行这个约定
The truth is, I've never actually taken him up on it.
直到遇到你  就走到了现在这一步
But then I met you, and here we are.
路易  拜托说句话
Louis, please say something.
给我点时间
I need a second.
如果你要走我完全理解
I-I understand if you want to go.
不  我愿意留下来
No. I'd like to stay.
你想去吃顿饭还是就喝点酒
Do you want to go for dinner or just drinks?
你想要什么
What do you want?
说实话吗  我宁愿找个小酒吧喝酒
The truth? I'd rather just go to a dive bar.
听起来不错
Sounds perfect to me.
爸爸  你来这做什么
Dad? What are you doing here?
我来跟你们俩谈谈
I came to talk to both of you.
什么事
What is it?
吉米・罗杰斯找到了你们要找的失踪的证人
Jim Rogers found your missing witness.
她三年前去世了
She died three years ago.
瞧瞧谁来了
Hey, look who it is.
我正要去电影之夜活动  加洛
I'm headed to movie night, Gallo.
我没时间在这纠缠
I don't have time for this.
不会花很多时间
This will just take a second.
你连片头都不会错过
I won't even make you miss the previews.
那我们赶紧说清楚完事
Let's get this over with.
我发现
It's been brought to my attention
今天哈维又一次来探望你而不是我
that Harvey came to visit you, not me, again today.
就像我之前跟你说的
And like I told you,
他来这是讨论我的案件
he came here to talk about my case.
你上次也是这么说的
Yeah, that's what you said the last time.
但我在想
But I got to thinking.
你已经达成了协议
And the thing is, you took a deal,
也就意味着你没有案件要考虑
which means you don't have a case.
加洛  我告诉你
Gallo, look, I'm telling you,
哈维正努力把你弄出去
Harvey is going to get you out.
这我知道
I know he is.
因为我知道你在这里做什么
Because I know what you're up to in here.
我知道的原因是因为我也在做同样的事
And the reason I know is because I did the same thing myself.
-你说什么呢  -你要告发你的室友
- What are you talking-- - You're informing on your roommate.
你都不知道自己在说什么  这是
You don't know what you're talking about. This is--
是吗  这里的每个人都知道
Don't I? Everybody in here knows
那家伙有事隐瞒
that guy's taken it out.
是个人都能想到你有机会知道真相
It doesn't take a genius to figure out you have access to him.
所以我调查了一下
So I did some checking.
原来哈维现在是那孩子岳父的代理
Turns out Harvey's representing the kid's daddy-in-law.
而我知道哈维会耍阴谋诡计
And I know Harvey does dirty tricks
因为他就是这么把我弄进来的
because that's what landed me in here.
-加洛  -你们想抓萨特
- Gallo-- - You guys are going after Sutter.
我很清楚  你也清楚
I know it, and you know it.
我还要告诉你
And I'll tell you something else,
你不快点把我弄出去
you don't get me out of here soon,
你的室友也要知道了
your bunkmate's gonna know it too.
肖恩  很好  你在这
Sean, good, you're here.
我需要你帮我做件事
I need you to do something for me
不过这事你不会很喜欢
and you're not gonna like it.
哈维  你先坐下
Harvey, I need you to sit down.
什么意思  干嘛要坐下
What do you mean, sit down?
他们取消了与迈克的交易
They pulled Mike's deal.
-你刚说什么  -哈维
- What did you just say to me? - Harvey--
因为你刚说的听起来
'Cause it sounded like you just said
就像你告诉我即使坚如磐石的东西
that think that you told me was rock solid
最后也不过狗屎一堆
was nothing more than a bucket of shit.
你想让我说什么
What do you want me to say?
我希望你说你会重新得到那份交易
I want you to say you'll get his deal back.
这我做不到  他们终止了交易
I can't do that. They pulled the plug.
真该死  是我逼他投向了你们
Goddamn it. I drove that guy to you.
你以为我不知道吗
Don't you think that I know that?
但如果我把事情告诉他们
But if I tell them that,
他们就会发现我们动过手脚
they're gonna know what we did.
那就不用菲利普・亚伦  放弃他
Then don't use Phillip Allen. Cut him loose,
让迈克帮你拿到需要的东西
and let Mike get you what you need.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
就算我愿意这么做
Even if I wanted to do that,
他们也不会让这个主要证人离开的
they're not gonna let their star witness get away.
你是部门老大
You are the head of the department.
他们都会听你的
They will listen to you.
你告诉他们这个家伙就只会胡说八道
You tell them this guy turned out to be full of shit.
那我就换句话说
Then let me put it a different way.
我不会让我的主要证人就这么离开
I'm not letting my star witness get away
因为我不会让那个混蛋
'cause I'm not letting that bastard get away
坑了别人的辛苦钱然后逍遥法外
with bilking people out of their hard-earned money.
肖恩  求你了
Sean, please,
一定还有别的办法能达到目的
there's gotta be another way to make this happen.
抱歉  哈维  恐怕没有
I'm sorry, Harvey. There isn't.
那从我的眼前消失
Then get the hell out of my sight.